So, here's our code again with the turtle's named
这就是我们的密码
consistently changed from George to Amy.
从乔治到艾米
Now line three says something about our turtle and the color
现在行三说我们的乌龟和颜色
yellow which makes sense when we look at what the program does,
当我们看看节目的内容时
it draws a yellow square.
它画了一个黄色的正方形
Now it's interesting that yellow is in quotes,
有趣的是黄色在引号中
nothing else in this program seems to be in quotes.
这个节目里没有别的东西在引号里
This line also has parentheses in it just like most of the other lines.
该行中的括号也与大多数其他行相似
Parentheses must be really important,
括号必须非常重要
there all over the place.
就在那里
Now, let's play with the code to see if we can figure out what more of these things do,.
现在 让我们一起玩这个代码 看看我们是否能想出更多这类的事情
That word Yellow really stands out.
那个黄字真的站出来了
Let's try changing it.
让我们试着改变它